let questions = [
    {
        question: "What body part did Yang lose in her first meeting with Adam?",
        answer: ["Right arm", "Left leg", "Her hair", "Wait... WHAT!!!"],
        correctAnswer: 'Right arm'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the nickname given to Jaune Arc in the first episode?",
        answer: ["Slugger", "Ladies-Man", "Vomit-Boy", "Useless-stick"],
        correctAnswer: 'Vomit-boy'
    },
    {
        question: "What happened to the moon?",
        answer: ["Always been like that", "Gods destroyed it", "Grimm Attack", "Asteroid Impact"],
        correctAnswer: 'Gods destroyed it'
    },
    {
        question:"Which character is not based on a Fairy Tale?",
        answer: ["Ren", "Ruby", "Hazel", "Weis"],
        correctAnswer: 'Ren'
    },
    {
        question:"Which character does not use a scythe weapon?",
        answer: ["Ruby Rose", "Qrow Branwen", "Maria Calavera", "Glynda Goodwitch"],
        correctAnswer: 'Glynda Goodwitch'
    },
    {
        question:"Which locker belongs to Jaune?",
        answer: ["616", "636", "239", "345"],
        correctAnswer: '636'
    },
    {
        question:"Where was Sunn raised?",
        answer: ["Mistral", "Vacuo", "Mantle", "Vale"],
        correctAnswer: 'Vacuo'
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the mother of Ruby?",
        answer: ["Summer", "Willow", "Kali", "rAVEN"],
        correctAnswer: 'Summer'
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the odd One out?",
        answer: ["ozma", "Oscar", "Ozpin", "Oobleck"],
        correctAnswer: 'Oobleck'
    },
    {
        question:"Pyrrha Nikos' weapon is what?",
        answer: ["Sword-lance and shield", "Warhammer", "Twin pistols", "Rifle trident"],
        correctAnswer: 'Sword-lance and shield'
    },
    //10 questions
    {
        question:"How many teammembers make up a standard team roster?",
        answer: ["3", "4", "5", "8"],
        correctAnswer: '4'
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the headmaster of Beacon academy?",
        answer: ["Ozpin", "Ironwood", "Taiyang", "Qrow"],
        correctAnswer: 'Ozpin'
    },
    {
        question:"What is the connection between Raven and Qrow?",
        answer: ["Husband and Wife", "Twin Siblings", "Father and Daughter", "Mother and Son"],
        correctAnswer: 'Twin Siblings'
    },
    {
        question:"Who was next in line to be the Fall maiden?",
        answer: ["Pyrrha", "Nora", "Yang", "Blake"],
        correctAnswer: 'Pyrrha'
    },
    {
        question:"Which Member of RWBY lived in Menagerie?",
        answer: ["Ruby", "Weiss", "Blake", "Yang"],
        correctAnswer: 'Blake'
    },
    {
        question:"What did team RWBY receive in the post from Taiyang?",
        answer: ["A load of washing", "A dog and his food", "Weapon repair kits", "Gushy family letters"],
        correctAnswer: 'A dog and his food'
    },
    {
        question:"Adam's surname is which member of the zodiac?",
        answer: ["Capricorn", "Virgo", "Taurus", "Leo"],
        correctAnswer: 'Taurus'
    },
    {
        question:"Who is robbing stores for their dust supplies?",
        answer: ["Roman", "Sun", "Cardin", "Velvet"],
        correctAnswer: 'Roman'
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the silent partner to Roman Torchwick?",
        answer: ["Neo", "Cinder", "Emerald", "Salem"],
        correctAnswer: 'Neo'
    },
    {
        question:"Which professor has probably had too many cups of coffee?",
        answer: ["Professor Port", "Doctor Oobleck", "Professor Goodwitch", "Professor Ozpin"],
        correctAnswer: 'Doctor Oobleck'
    },
    //20 question

    {
        question:"In the Vale fighting festival, who fights against Pyrrha?",
        answer: ["Sunn", "Emerald", "Yang", "Penny"],
        correctAnswer: 'Penny'
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the only artificial being who can generate aura?",
        answer: ["Penny Polendina", "Nora Valyrie", "Weiss Schnee", "Cinder Fall"],
        correctAnswer: 'Penny Polendina'
    },
    {
        question:"How many gods were there when Salem los her true love?",
        answer: ["4", "3", "2", "1"],
        correctAnswer: '2'
    },
    {
        question:"What is the main produce of Weiss' family business?",
        answer: ["Food", "Guns", "Clothes", "Dust"],
        correctAnswer: 'Dust'
    },
    {
        question:"What is located in the vault under Haven Academy?",
        answer: ["Staff of Creation", "Relic of Knowledge", "The Fall Maiden", "Ozpin's Favourite Books"],
        correctAnswer: 'Relic of Knowledge'
    },
    {
        question:"What is the alter ego of Maria Calavera?",
        answer: ["Grimm Reaper", "Shorty-Pants", "Spring Maiden", "Dust Sorceress"],
        correctAnswer: 'Grimm Reaper'
    },
    {
        question:"Yang leaves to find Ruby, But who is it she is actually looking for?",
        answer: ["Qrow", "Raven", "Robyn", "Yuma"],
        correctAnswer: 'Raven'
    },
    {
        question:"What is the team name Nora creates when rwby joins them?",
        answer: ["JNRR", "RNJR", "NRJR", "Where's the P gone?"],
        correctAnswer: 'JNRR'
    },
    {
        question:"Where does the battle between Cinder and Pyrrha come to a dramatic end?",
        answer: ["Amity Colusseum", "Beacon Tower", "Haven Academy", "Vale Docks"],
        correctAnswer: 'Beacon Tower'
    },
    {
        question:"What does Oscar do before Ozpin joins him?",
        answer: ["Student", "Beggar", "Shop clerk", "Farmhand"],
        correctAnswer: 'Farmhand'
    },
    //30 questions

    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    // 40 questions

    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        question:"?",
        answer: ["", "", "", ""],
        correctAnswer: ''
    },
    //50 questions
]